<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>meta on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meta on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025 Wrap Up Post</title>
      <link>/posts/2026-01-10_2025-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2026-01-10_2025-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            So, I guess there goes 2025. I’m a bit late on the wrap up post, though as much as I’d like to blame a cold I’ve been dealing with for a while (lol I wrote that several days ago when drafting, and I&amp;rsquo;ve still just now gotten around to posting my finished draft), it’s mostly just laziness. All things considered, it’s been a pretty eventful year for myself - namely that I left my job and returned to my home state.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024 Writing Retrospective</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-12-30_2024-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-12-30_2024-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Another wild and wacky year is wrapping up, and with it the customary year end wrap up/retrospective. This year I posted a total of 11 posts1, two being update/revised posts and nine standalone posts. My longest post (by far) was my revised microblogging comparison post at 15,411 words2 3, and my shortest was my pickles/sauerkraut recipe post at 722 words (the only post under 1k words). My average post length was 4991 words, my median post length being a similar 5169 words.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging in 2023</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-01-18_2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-01-18_2023-review/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            It is (or was at least) a new year and I thought I would reflect on my 2023 posts and talk about what kind of content I follow. I originally thought about doing this on Dec 31st, but I tend to work pretty slowly on posts so here I am whenever this actually gets finished and goes live. Since June I posted a total of thirteen posts, two of which were more generic updates (a quick first post and a notice about a URL change), which leaves me a little under two posts per month.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
