<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Updates on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/categories/personal-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Updates on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/personal-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025 Wrap Up Post</title>
      <link>/posts/2026-01-10_2025-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2026-01-10_2025-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            So, I guess there goes 2025. I’m a bit late on the wrap up post, though as much as I’d like to blame a cold I’ve been dealing with for a while (lol I wrote that several days ago when drafting, and I&amp;rsquo;ve still just now gotten around to posting my finished draft), it’s mostly just laziness. All things considered, it’s been a pretty eventful year for myself - namely that I left my job and returned to my home state.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2025 Defaults</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-12-09_defaults-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-12-09_defaults-2025/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            In 2023 Robb Knight started the defaults trend, covering what people used as their default apps for specific purposes. I did a 2023 version, and while I mentioned planning to do a late 2024 version in my 2024 year end wrap up post, I never wound up getting to it. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a 2025 edition of my default apps below, with changes in bold.
PC Tablet Phone Mail Client Proton Web N/A Proton App Mail Server ^ ^ ^ Notes Joplin Joplin Joplin Tasks N/A N/A Tasks (org.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anyone out there hiring? &#43; 10 pointless facts</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-10-31_random-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-10-31_random-update/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I was thinking about making a personal update, then saw a post on Joelchrono’s blog about the 10 useless facts about me challenge, so I thought I’d combine both of those into one post.
Fairly recently, I left my job to relocate back to my home state of New York, and have been looking for work more locally. I kind of expected work to be a bit hard to come by, and planned accordingly, but that still doesn’t make the job search any less of a slog.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024 Writing Retrospective</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-12-30_2024-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-12-30_2024-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Another wild and wacky year is wrapping up, and with it the customary year end wrap up/retrospective. This year I posted a total of 11 posts1, two being update/revised posts and nine standalone posts. My longest post (by far) was my revised microblogging comparison post at 15,411 words2 3, and my shortest was my pickles/sauerkraut recipe post at 722 words (the only post under 1k words). My average post length was 4991 words, my median post length being a similar 5169 words.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging in 2023</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-01-18_2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-01-18_2023-review/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            It is (or was at least) a new year and I thought I would reflect on my 2023 posts and talk about what kind of content I follow. I originally thought about doing this on Dec 31st, but I tend to work pretty slowly on posts so here I am whenever this actually gets finished and goes live. Since June I posted a total of thirteen posts, two of which were more generic updates (a quick first post and a notice about a URL change), which leaves me a little under two posts per month.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain Change</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR Even though it&amp;rsquo;s only been three months since I created my blog here, I&amp;rsquo;m going to change the domain from www.mecca1.net to nate.mecca1.net instead. Nothing&amp;rsquo;s should break, www.mecca1.net will forward to nate.mecca1.net for now. Still, if you&amp;rsquo;re following me through RSS or you have my site bookmarked it might be worth swapping out the URL.
Longer Update My domain predates my blog by about six years, so when I created my blog a few months ago I opted to just use the www subdomain.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to start a blog here. I got this domain with some DNS records just collecting dust, and have an interest in writing stuff casually. I figure I&amp;rsquo;ll write about projects I work on or opinions about things in my field whenever something interests me enough to talk about it. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t write too much about myself personally though, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this you probably A) know me already and somehow got roped into reading this, B) we&amp;rsquo;re working on some sort of project and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading about my writing about it, or C) find my writing about something interesting or useful (the latter being the most unlikely).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
