<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Random Tech Tidbits if the Lights (or Router) Goes Out</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I count myself lucky to live in a pretty stable and safe part of the world. The last three years or so might have been slightly less so, but still in the scheme of things I certainly haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the worst of it. But hey, this year is as good of any to think about useful ways to utilize your electronics, specifically your phone, if the power goes out or something similar happens.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain Change</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR Even though it&amp;rsquo;s only been three months since I created my blog here, I&amp;rsquo;m going to change the domain from www.mecca1.net to nate.mecca1.net instead. Nothing&amp;rsquo;s should break, www.mecca1.net will forward to nate.mecca1.net for now. Still, if you&amp;rsquo;re following me through RSS or you have my site bookmarked it might be worth swapping out the URL.
Longer Update My domain predates my blog by about six years, so when I created my blog a few months ago I opted to just use the www subdomain.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IPFS &#43; basic use</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            IPFS, an acronym for &amp;ldquo;InterPlanetary File System&amp;rdquo;, is a way to deliver files that takes a different approach to HTTP. As I mentioned in my very first post, I originally considered hosting my entire site/blog on it, and while I decided against it for reasons I mentioned there and reasons I&amp;rsquo;ll get into later here; I am working on something that may involve me sharing files here, which I&amp;rsquo;ll probably use IPFS for.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#39;s All-Cloud Windows is what I dislike about Modern Computing</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I never have had a good track record with massive changes to Windows, starting with Windows 8 which was entirely unusable in my case. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the mobile-style graphics and the bloat, but also the fact I couldn’t get more than a couple of days before the installation would break. This went on for a while as I tried to figure out why it was breaking, and I probably went through dozens of installs that themselves took nearly as long as the time I could actually use the device before it broke again.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to start a blog here. I got this domain with some DNS records just collecting dust, and have an interest in writing stuff casually. I figure I&amp;rsquo;ll write about projects I work on or opinions about things in my field whenever something interests me enough to talk about it. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t write too much about myself personally though, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this you probably A) know me already and somehow got roped into reading this, B) we&amp;rsquo;re working on some sort of project and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading about my writing about it, or C) find my writing about something interesting or useful (the latter being the most unlikely).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
