<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debian on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/debian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debian on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/debian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The RAM wars: mini penguin to the rescue</title>
      <link>/posts/2026-02-01_old-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2026-02-01_old-laptop/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Originally, I was drafting this in September, planning on dedicating it to Windows 10 Home becoming EOL. I also figured I’d share a meme that contained something along the following:
Instead, however, it’s early 2026, and I feel like a dedication to RAM prices would be a more fitting start:
Memes aside, the lightweight laptop - what I’m typing this post on - has a whopping total of 2 GB of ram (1.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 2</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            This is my second post about searching for a tablet, and a follow-up review of the device I mentioned purchasing in the last post (an MS Surface Go tablet). Aside from the fact I just find it relaxing to write about things that interest or affect me, I hope that this would be useful if you&amp;rsquo;re considering buying an MS Surface tablet (to run either Win/Linux), or if you&amp;rsquo;re purchasing a different tablet to run Linux and want to know how a potential configuration might look.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 1</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR, for those looking for less of a novel I did a lot of looking and found a few different options if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tablet and have similar preferences as me. There are custom ROMs for some tablets, though they are somewhat limited in which devices are supported (as well as sometimes limits on features or time in which security updates come in). There&amp;rsquo;s also the ability to cut out junk with ADB bridge on Android tablets, of which some cheaper tablets are sketchy and lack long-term security updates, and some of the premium tablets can get pricey.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
