<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>complaints on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/categories/complaints/</link>
    <description>Recent content in complaints on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/categories/complaints/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MITM Risks in Signal? Mitigation &#43; Monologue</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update 11/25: I was made aware that Signal has some proprietary anti-spam code and added the TLDR.
A More Technical TLDR I never know how much jargon I should include or how much I should explain, and as long as I&amp;rsquo;m writing I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying myself meaning I&amp;rsquo;ve been all over the place. But here&amp;rsquo;s a shortened version for those familiar with encryption.
A vanilla implementation of the Signal protocol relies on public key infrastructure to perform a handshake between devices.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#39;s All-Cloud Windows is what I dislike about Modern Computing</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I never have had a good track record with massive changes to Windows, starting with Windows 8 which was entirely unusable in my case. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the mobile-style graphics and the bloat, but also the fact I couldn’t get more than a couple of days before the installation would break. This went on for a while as I tried to figure out why it was breaking, and I probably went through dozens of installs that themselves took nearly as long as the time I could actually use the device before it broke again.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
