<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>atproto on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/atproto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in atproto on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/atproto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This is Fine: an Interim Microblogging Protocols Update</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-12-07_microblog-protocols-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-12-07_microblog-protocols-update/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            As is customary on my microblogging posts, let&amp;rsquo;s get us started with an original meme. Also, if you&amp;rsquo;d like to read my previous Microblogging Protocols compared posts, you can read v1 here and v2 here.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over a year since I made my updated microblogging protocols comparison. Since then a few things have happened, and my previous could use some trimming. In the spirit of keeping things shorter (and keeping the comparison v3 post relevant longer), I figured I&amp;rsquo;d split the post into two parts: this one, which includes random updates and things that happened over the last year or so - and a second one, &amp;ldquo;Microblogging Protocols Compared v3&amp;rdquo; which will be a more streamlined protocol comparison.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microblogging Protocols Compared v2</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update: September 20th, 2024: I was incorrect regarding AT&amp;rsquo;s (BlueSky) inability to fully delete things, the protocol DOES support fully deleting posts from the user&amp;rsquo;s repo and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the post to reflect that. Read more. Big thanks to Ryan for providing the info.
Also, on a less important update (in regards to this post&amp;rsquo;s accuracy) - in keeping tradition with the original post - Bluesky has managed to change rapidly shortly after I finished this.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivityPub/Nostr/AT-BlueSky Compared</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Note: This post is out of date, here&amp;rsquo;s a more up to date version
Update August 5th 2024
I have some good and bad news regarding this post. First, I made two mistakes. AT crawlers are not in fact crawlers, they are called relays. Also, shared inboxes are actually part of the Activity Pub W3C standard as apposed to hacky additions to the protocol by third party servers. I was wrong about Activity Pub servers sending multiple messages to the same server remote to update it about a single post.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
