<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>windows on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in windows on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 2</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            This is my second post about searching for a tablet, and a follow-up review of the device I mentioned purchasing in the last post (an MS Surface Go tablet). Aside from the fact I just find it relaxing to write about things that interest or affect me, I hope that this would be useful if you&amp;rsquo;re considering buying an MS Surface tablet (to run either Win/Linux), or if you&amp;rsquo;re purchasing a different tablet to run Linux and want to know how a potential configuration might look.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 1</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR, for those looking for less of a novel I did a lot of looking and found a few different options if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tablet and have similar preferences as me. There are custom ROMs for some tablets, though they are somewhat limited in which devices are supported (as well as sometimes limits on features or time in which security updates come in). There&amp;rsquo;s also the ability to cut out junk with ADB bridge on Android tablets, of which some cheaper tablets are sketchy and lack long-term security updates, and some of the premium tablets can get pricey.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get The Most of Win 11 (and the least bloat)</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            11/03/2023 Update: I fixed some grammar, and Google just announced they&amp;rsquo;re going to stop the implementation of WEI (hopefully permanently, but they may just be trying to outwait bad publicity and anti-trust actions - only time will tell).
If you read my first post here you probably got the idea I have strong feelings about recent versions of Windows, and you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be wrong. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of junk on Windows, but there are many ways you can go around and clean up some of the worst of it, and I thought I would go over a few potential ways of doing so.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#39;s All-Cloud Windows is what I dislike about Modern Computing</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I never have had a good track record with massive changes to Windows, starting with Windows 8 which was entirely unusable in my case. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the mobile-style graphics and the bloat, but also the fact I couldn’t get more than a couple of days before the installation would break. This went on for a while as I tried to figure out why it was breaking, and I probably went through dozens of installs that themselves took nearly as long as the time I could actually use the device before it broke again.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
