<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nostr on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/nostr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nostr on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/nostr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This is Fine: an Interim Microblogging Protocols Update</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-12-07_microblog-protocols-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-12-07_microblog-protocols-update/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            As is customary on my microblogging posts, let&amp;rsquo;s get us started with an original meme. Also, if you&amp;rsquo;d like to read my previous Microblogging Protocols compared posts, you can read v1 here and v2 here.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over a year since I made my updated microblogging protocols comparison. Since then a few things have happened, and my previous could use some trimming. In the spirit of keeping things shorter (and keeping the comparison v3 post relevant longer), I figured I&amp;rsquo;d split the post into two parts: this one, which includes random updates and things that happened over the last year or so - and a second one, &amp;ldquo;Microblogging Protocols Compared v3&amp;rdquo; which will be a more streamlined protocol comparison.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFTs and Dark Web Shenanagins</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-06-18_standard-server-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-06-18_standard-server-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            A based design that makes a web that&amp;rsquo;s true
ICANNs and NATs embrace shall be no more
Behind a Pi or in the cloud for you
We use that tool be I2P or Tor
Come join a world of speech that can flow free
The words by truths of math they shall be bound
A power built right in that&amp;rsquo;s DHT
Identity by key pairs holds its ground
IPFS a poggers web design
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vibe Coding Chronicles</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-04-13_vibe-coding-chronicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2025-04-13_vibe-coding-chronicles/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            POV: You&amp;rsquo;re a professional dev watching me talk about vibe coding: Your browser does not support the video tag. I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly a stranger to using AI code, parts of nipy-bridge like the part that handles posts based on size was written by Chat GPT via Duck.AI, and I regularly use a Mixtral-Dolphin written bash script to convert files with avifenc. Recently, however, I came across Bookstr by MK Fain, which is being vibe coded.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microblogging Protocols Compared v2</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update: September 20th, 2024: I was incorrect regarding AT&amp;rsquo;s (BlueSky) inability to fully delete things, the protocol DOES support fully deleting posts from the user&amp;rsquo;s repo and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the post to reflect that. Read more. Big thanks to Ryan for providing the info.
Also, on a less important update (in regards to this post&amp;rsquo;s accuracy) - in keeping tradition with the original post - Bluesky has managed to change rapidly shortly after I finished this.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a client, Nostr surpassed Mastodon, and BlueSky is open?</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            So after two very long posts, one complaining about web browsers and one comparing the three big non-centralized social media protocols, I thought about writing two shorter posts about random things (hats and making sour krout specifically). However, between then and now stuffs happened and I thought I would make an anthology post with three different mini topics I wanted to share.
I made a client So yeah, I made a client that can post to Nostr, Activity Pub, and BlueSky (hopefully all of AT once it&amp;rsquo;s fully opened).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivityPub/Nostr/AT-BlueSky Compared</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Note: This post is out of date, here&amp;rsquo;s a more up to date version
Update August 5th 2024
I have some good and bad news regarding this post. First, I made two mistakes. AT crawlers are not in fact crawlers, they are called relays. Also, shared inboxes are actually part of the Activity Pub W3C standard as apposed to hacky additions to the protocol by third party servers. I was wrong about Activity Pub servers sending multiple messages to the same server remote to update it about a single post.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostr</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I have recently been re-dipping my toes into Nostr (tried it a while back just to experiment with it but never really stuck around), and so far it&amp;rsquo;s become my preferred microblogging platform. There&amp;rsquo;s a handful of reasons surrounding that, both in the protocol itself and what&amp;rsquo;s being built up around it, and I think it has a lot of promise that merits its very quick growth. Today I thought I would go over why I am a fan of it, and why I think it might be worth checking out if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in a more decentralized web.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
