<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nostr on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/nostr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nostr on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/nostr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microblogging Protocols Compared v2</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Click Here to skip my introduction and the misc topics.
In January of 2024 I published a blog post comparing Activity Pub, Nostr, and AT, and this is a revised version of that post. There are a few reasons why I went about making an updated version. First, I got a couple of things wrong - specifically not realizing SharedInboxes were part of the official Activity Pub standard and mistakenly calling AT relays AT crawlers.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a client, Nostr surpassed Mastodon, and BlueSky is open?</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            So after two very long posts, one complaining about web browsers and one comparing the three big non-centralized social media protocols, I thought about writing two shorter posts about random things (hats and making sour krout specifically). However, between then and now stuffs happened and I thought I would make an anthology post with three different mini topics I wanted to share.
I made a client So yeah, I made a client that can post to Nostr, Activity Pub, and BlueSky (hopefully all of AT once it&amp;rsquo;s fully opened).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivityPub/Nostr/AT-BlueSky Compared</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Note: This post is out of date, here&amp;rsquo;s a more up to date version
Update August 5th 2024
I have some good and bad news regarding this post. First, I made two mistakes. AT crawlers are not in fact crawlers, they are called relays. Also, shared inboxes are actually part of the Activity Pub W3C standard as apposed to hacky additions to the protocol by third party servers. I was wrong about Activity Pub servers sending multiple messages to the same server remote to update it about a single post.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostr</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I have recently been re-dipping my toes into Nostr (tried it a while back just to experiment with it but never really stuck around), and so far it&amp;rsquo;s become my preferred microblogging platform. There&amp;rsquo;s a handful of reasons surrounding that, both in the protocol itself and what&amp;rsquo;s being built up around it, and I think it has a lot of promise that merits its very quick growth. Today I thought I would go over why I am a fan of it, and why I think it might be worth checking out if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in a more decentralized web.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
