<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>protocols on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/protocols/</link>
    <description>Recent content in protocols on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/protocols/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microblogging Protocols Compared v2</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-08-11_microbloggingv2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update: September 20th, 2024: I was incorrect regarding AT&amp;rsquo;s (BlueSky) inability to fully delete things, the protocol DOES support fully deleting posts from the user&amp;rsquo;s repo and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the post to reflect that. Read more. Big thanks to Ryan for providing the info.
Also, on a less important update (in regards to this post&amp;rsquo;s accuracy) - in keeping tradition with the original post - Bluesky has managed to change rapidly shortly after I finished this.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a client, Nostr surpassed Mastodon, and BlueSky is open?</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-02-24_microblogging-anthology/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            So after two very long posts, one complaining about web browsers and one comparing the three big non-centralized social media protocols, I thought about writing two shorter posts about random things (hats and making sour krout specifically). However, between then and now stuffs happened and I thought I would make an anthology post with three different mini topics I wanted to share.
I made a client So yeah, I made a client that can post to Nostr, Activity Pub, and BlueSky (hopefully all of AT once it&amp;rsquo;s fully opened).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivityPub/Nostr/AT-BlueSky Compared</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-01-30_microblogging-protocols/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Note: This post is out of date, here&amp;rsquo;s a more up to date version
Update August 5th 2024
I have some good and bad news regarding this post. First, I made two mistakes. AT crawlers are not in fact crawlers, they are called relays. Also, shared inboxes are actually part of the Activity Pub W3C standard as apposed to hacky additions to the protocol by third party servers. I was wrong about Activity Pub servers sending multiple messages to the same server remote to update it about a single post.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Agnostic Following</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Chances are if you&amp;rsquo;re here it&amp;rsquo;s through an RSS feed (or an RSS feed bridged to something else), so I probably don&amp;rsquo;t need to do too much of an introduction. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick rundown if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar. However, today I wanted to talk about RSS (as well as three other means of following content), how I&amp;rsquo;ve benefited from it, and a small project I started. Just about every piece of content I follow is through RSS - organized into different categories (news, blogs, videos, audio, etc), and the following benefits really stand out:
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostr</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I have recently been re-dipping my toes into Nostr (tried it a while back just to experiment with it but never really stuck around), and so far it&amp;rsquo;s become my preferred microblogging platform. There&amp;rsquo;s a handful of reasons surrounding that, both in the protocol itself and what&amp;rsquo;s being built up around it, and I think it has a lot of promise that merits its very quick growth. Today I thought I would go over why I am a fan of it, and why I think it might be worth checking out if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in a more decentralized web.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MITM Risks in Signal? Mitigation &#43; Monologue</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update 11/25: I was made aware that Signal has some proprietary anti-spam code and added the TLDR.
A More Technical TLDR I never know how much jargon I should include or how much I should explain, and as long as I&amp;rsquo;m writing I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying myself meaning I&amp;rsquo;ve been all over the place. But here&amp;rsquo;s a shortened version for those familiar with encryption.
A vanilla implementation of the Signal protocol relies on public key infrastructure to perform a handshake between devices.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IPFS &#43; basic use</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            IPFS, an acronym for &amp;ldquo;InterPlanetary File System&amp;rdquo;, is a way to deliver files that takes a different approach to HTTP. As I mentioned in my very first post, I originally considered hosting my entire site/blog on it, and while I decided against it for reasons I mentioned there and reasons I&amp;rsquo;ll get into later here; I am working on something that may involve me sharing files here, which I&amp;rsquo;ll probably use IPFS for.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
