<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>informational on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/categories/informational/</link>
    <description>Recent content in informational on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/categories/informational/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get The Most of Win 11 (and the least bloat)</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Get The Most of Win 11 (and the least bloat)
If you read my first post here you probably got the idea I have strong feelings about recent versions of Windows, and you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be wrong. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of junk on Windows, but there are many ways you can go around and clean up some of the worst of it, and I thought I would go over a few potential ways of doing so.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tech Tidbits if the Lights (or Router) Goes Out</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I count myself lucky to live in a pretty stable and safe part of the world. The last three years or so might have been slightly less so, but still in the scheme of things I certainly haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the worst of it. But hey, this year is as good of any to think about useful ways to utilize your electronics, specifically your phone, if the power goes out or something similar happens.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IPFS &#43; basic use</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            IPFS, an acronym for &amp;ldquo;InterPlanetary File System&amp;rdquo;, is a way to deliver files that takes a different approach to HTTP. As I mentioned in my very first post, I originally considered hosting my entire site/blog on it, and while I decided against it for reasons I mentioned there and reasons I&amp;rsquo;ll get into later here; I am working on something that may involve me sharing files here, which I&amp;rsquo;ll probably use IPFS for.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
