<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Platform Agnostic Following</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Chances are if you&amp;rsquo;re here it&amp;rsquo;s through an RSS feed (or an RSS feed bridged to something else), so I probably don&amp;rsquo;t need to do too much of an introduction. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick rundown if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar. However, today I wanted to talk about RSS (as well as three other means of following content), how I&amp;rsquo;ve benefited from it, and a small project I started. Just about every piece of content I follow is through RSS - organized into different categories (news, blogs, videos, audio, etc), and the following benefits really stand out:
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostr</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-11_nostr/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I have recently been re-dipping my toes into Nostr (tried it a while back just to experiment with it but never really stuck around), and so far it&amp;rsquo;s become my preferred microblogging platform. There&amp;rsquo;s a handful of reasons surrounding that, both in the protocol itself and what&amp;rsquo;s being built up around it, and I think it has a lot of promise that merits its very quick growth. Today I thought I would go over why I am a fan of it, and why I think it might be worth checking out if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in a more decentralized web.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 2</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-12-01_tablets-2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            This is my second post about searching for a tablet, and a follow-up review of the device I mentioned purchasing in the last post (an MS Surface Go tablet). Aside from the fact I just find it relaxing to write about things that interest or affect me, I hope that this would be useful if you&amp;rsquo;re considering buying an MS Surface tablet (to run either Win/Linux), or if you&amp;rsquo;re purchasing a different tablet to run Linux and want to know how a potential configuration might look.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MITM Risks in Signal? Mitigation &#43; Monologue</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-19_signal-cons/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Update 11/25: I was made aware that Signal has some proprietary anti-spam code and added the TLDR.
A More Technical TLDR I never know how much jargon I should include or how much I should explain, and as long as I&amp;rsquo;m writing I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying myself meaning I&amp;rsquo;ve been all over the place. But here&amp;rsquo;s a shortened version for those familiar with encryption.
A vanilla implementation of the Signal protocol relies on public key infrastructure to perform a handshake between devices.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defaults</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-14_defaults/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-14_defaults/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I ran across a neat trend of sharing your default apps, and a collection of posts doing so. It&amp;rsquo;s made some interesting reads and I thought I would join in and post my own favorites.
My Devices I have three different devices: a PC running Debian, a tablet I just got setup running Debian and a Waydroid container, and a phone running the Graphene fork of Android. PC Tablet Phone 📨 Mail Client Proton Web Proton App Proton App 📮 Mail Server ^ ^ ^ 📝 Notes Joplin Joplin Joplin ✅ To-Do n/a n/a Tasks (F-Droid) 📷 Photo Shooting n/a n/a AOSP Camera 🟦 Photo Management File Manager n/a AOSP Gallery 📆 Calendar n/a n/a Simple Calendar 📁 Cloud File Storage IceDrive (web) IceDrive (web) IceDrive (PWA) 📖 RSS Nextcloud (web) Nextcloud (web) Nextcloud News App 🙍🏻‍♂️ Contacts n/a n/a AOSP Contacts 🌐 Browser LibreWolf Brave Fennec Firefox 💬 Chat Matrix &amp;gt; Signal &amp;gt; Telegram &amp;gt; G Chat (Web) Matrix &amp;gt; Signal &amp;gt; Telegram &amp;gt; G Chat (Web) Matrix &amp;gt; Signal &amp;gt; Telegram &amp;gt; G Chat (Web) 🔖 Bookmarks Unsynced Unsynced Unsynced 📑 Read It Later PDFs w/ Syncthing PDFs w/ Syncthing PDFs w/ Syncthing 📜 Word Processing LibreOffice LibreOffice n/a 📈 Spreadsheets LibreOffice n/a n/a 📊 Presentations LibreOffice n/a n/a 🛒 Shopping Lists Joplin Joplin Joplin 🍴 Meal Planning n/a n/a n/a 💰 Budgeting and Personal Finance n/a n/a MoneyWallet 📰 News Nextcloud (Web) Nextcould (Web) Nextcloud News App 🎵 Music VLC VLC Innertune 🎤 Podcasts VLC VLC VLC 🔐 Password Management Keepass Keepass Keepass The above is the pre-built list, though for my post I thought I would add on a few extras I like:
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quest to find a tablet, pt 1</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-05_tablets-1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR, for those looking for less of a novel I did a lot of looking and found a few different options if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tablet and have similar preferences as me. There are custom ROMs for some tablets, though they are somewhat limited in which devices are supported (as well as sometimes limits on features or time in which security updates come in). There&amp;rsquo;s also the ability to cut out junk with ADB bridge on Android tablets, of which some cheaper tablets are sketchy and lack long-term security updates, and some of the premium tablets can get pricey.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get The Most of Win 11 (and the least bloat)</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-11-02_win11/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            11/03/2023 Update: I fixed some grammar, and Google just announced they&amp;rsquo;re going to stop the implementation of WEI (hopefully permanently, but they may just be trying to outwait bad publicity and anti-trust actions - only time will tell).
If you read my first post here you probably got the idea I have strong feelings about recent versions of Windows, and you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be wrong. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of junk on Windows, but there are many ways you can go around and clean up some of the worst of it, and I thought I would go over a few potential ways of doing so.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tech Tidbits if the Lights (or Router) Goes Out</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-10-23_cell-down/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I count myself lucky to live in a pretty stable and safe part of the world. The last three years or so might have been slightly less so, but still in the scheme of things I certainly haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the worst of it. But hey, this year is as good of any to think about useful ways to utilize your electronics, specifically your phone, if the power goes out or something similar happens.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain Change</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR Even though it&amp;rsquo;s only been three months since I created my blog here, I&amp;rsquo;m going to change the domain from www.mecca1.net to nate.mecca1.net instead. Nothing&amp;rsquo;s should break, www.mecca1.net will forward to nate.mecca1.net for now. Still, if you&amp;rsquo;re following me through RSS or you have my site bookmarked it might be worth swapping out the URL.
Longer Update My domain predates my blog by about six years, so when I created my blog a few months ago I opted to just use the www subdomain.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IPFS &#43; basic use</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-08-28_ipfs/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            IPFS, an acronym for &amp;ldquo;InterPlanetary File System&amp;rdquo;, is a way to deliver files that takes a different approach to HTTP. As I mentioned in my very first post, I originally considered hosting my entire site/blog on it, and while I decided against it for reasons I mentioned there and reasons I&amp;rsquo;ll get into later here; I am working on something that may involve me sharing files here, which I&amp;rsquo;ll probably use IPFS for.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#39;s All-Cloud Windows is what I dislike about Modern Computing</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-07-24_cloud-oss/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I never have had a good track record with massive changes to Windows, starting with Windows 8 which was entirely unusable in my case. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the mobile-style graphics and the bloat, but also the fact I couldn’t get more than a couple of days before the installation would break. This went on for a while as I tried to figure out why it was breaking, and I probably went through dozens of installs that themselves took nearly as long as the time I could actually use the device before it broke again.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to start a blog here. I got this domain with some DNS records just collecting dust, and have an interest in writing stuff casually. I figure I&amp;rsquo;ll write about projects I work on or opinions about things in my field whenever something interests me enough to talk about it. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t write too much about myself personally though, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this you probably A) know me already and somehow got roped into reading this, B) we&amp;rsquo;re working on some sort of project and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading about my writing about it, or C) find my writing about something interesting or useful (the latter being the most unlikely).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
