<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making a Fur Hat</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-09-09_hats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-09-09_hats/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            In my post about EDC I rambled on about hats for a bit, and a couple weeks ago I decided to try making one myself. I didn&amp;rsquo;t initially plan on writing a blog post explaining how I did it; however, after having trouble finding a printable pattern, I wound up just winging it, and I figured I&amp;rsquo;d put my process out there.1 Fur hats are way warmer than just about anything else, and even though this was a trial run with a fake polyester fur pelt it&amp;rsquo;s still a warm hat on its own.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDC, Watches, &amp; Tactical Sporks</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-08-05_edc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-08-05_edc/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Dropdown: Random notes from drafting Alright, it is April 2nd and I&amp;rsquo;m typing out the first couple of characters in this document which I can already guess is going to be another long post. I already have tons of posts that I expected to be medium length which ballooned out, so given I know ahead of time it&amp;rsquo;ll be long who knows how long it will be. Err, well, editing me and you the reader will know how long it is when I actually publish it.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of a Data Hoarder</title>
      <link>/posts/2024-05-20_archiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2024-05-20_archiving/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Okay, so I&amp;rsquo;m not actually sure I would consider myself a data hoarder, but I thought the title was pretty eye catching, and archival is close enough to data hoarding to only be moderately clickbaity. (I actually think I&amp;rsquo;ve got a pretty well organized and reasonably trimmed home directory). Anyway, I thought I would go over a couple of related topics, specifically my backup strategy, some data archiving, and me getting back into useing optical storage.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Agnostic Following</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-12-20_followanything/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Chances are if you&amp;rsquo;re here it&amp;rsquo;s through an RSS feed (or an RSS feed bridged to something else), so I probably don&amp;rsquo;t need to do too much of an introduction. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick rundown if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar. However, today I wanted to talk about RSS (as well as three other means of following content), how I&amp;rsquo;ve benefited from it, and a small project I started. Just about every piece of content I follow is through RSS - organized into different categories (news, blogs, videos, audio, etc), and the following benefits really stand out:
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
