<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>misc on An Untitled Blog</title>
    <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in misc on An Untitled Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nate.mecca1.net/tags/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain Change</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-09-24_subdomain-change/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            TLDR Even though it&amp;rsquo;s only been three months since I created my blog here, I&amp;rsquo;m going to change the domain from www.mecca1.net to nate.mecca1.net instead. Nothing&amp;rsquo;s going to break, www.mecca1.net will just auto-forward for now to nate.mecca1.net once I change it. Still, if you&amp;rsquo;re following me through RSS or you have my site bookmarked it might be worth swapping out the URL.
Longer Update My domain predates my blog by about six years, so when I created my blog a few months ago I opted to just use the www subdomain.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nate.mecca1.net/posts/2023-06-16_first-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to start a blog here. I got this domain with some DNS records just collecting dust, and have an interest in writing stuff casually. I figure I&amp;rsquo;ll write about projects I work on or opinions about things in my field whenever something interests me enough to talk about it. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t write too much about myself personally though, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this you probably A) know me already and somehow got roped into reading this, B) we&amp;rsquo;re working on some sort of project and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading about my writing about it, or C) find my writing about something interesting or useful (the latter being the most unlikely).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
